<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://amjadrathod.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Contact Our TeamThe Backgrounds Online team is friendly, industry-educated and here to help. Contact us for a quick response.Hours: Mon – Fri, 5:00am – 5:00pm (PT)
Telephone: 1-800-838-4804 Fax: 1-800-838-4654
Email: support@backgroundsonline.com
Chat:=0 ? &#39;&amp;amp;&#39; : &#39;?&#39;) + &#39;url=&#39; + escape(document.location.href)), &#39;Chat7264917492266979376&#39;, &#39;toolbar=0,scrollbars=1,location=0,statusbar=0,menubar=0,resizable=1,width=640,height=480&#39;);return false;&#34;
Backgrounds Online
1915 21st St.
Sacramento, CA 95811
-Select State-AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/dispute-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/dispute-results/</guid>
      <description>Dispute The Results Of Your Background CheckIf you feel the information on your background check was inaccurate, please contact us. The Fair Credit Reporting Act (FCRA) entitles you to dispute your results.Our team of Background Screening Specialists will review the information you wish to dispute and go directly to the source to find current, accurate information. We will also inform the company that requested a background check on you thatyou filed a dispute and provide them with updated background screening results if revisions are made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/faqs/</guid>
      <description>FAQ&#39;sGetting StartedHow much does your service cost?Do you charge monthly fees?How quickly can I get started?Can I create a screening account online?What information will I need to sign up online?I am a Notary. Should I start my own screening account?My AccountWhat information do I need from an applicant to run a background check?Can my applicant submit their own information for a background check?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/industry-background-check/financial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/industry-background-check/financial/</guid>
      <description>Background Checks
for the Financial IndustryReduce Your Hiring RisksHiring someone who is not qualified for a financial position can lead to unexpected expenses and additional hiring cycles. Poor hiring decisions could also damage your reputation. It is imperative to select trustworthy, capablecandidates to represent your business. To help, we offer Custom Background Checks that can be tailored to suit any position. You can save them for future use to reduce your hiring risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/industry-background-check/insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/industry-background-check/insurance/</guid>
      <description>Background Checks
for the Insurance IndustryInsurance Companies Face Hiring IssuesThe insurance industry is constantly in need of people. It can be difficult to find personnel for all your staffing needs. That makes it even more important to employ eligible, reliable candidates. If you skip the background screeningprocess, you may hire someone who is not qualified to represent your company and end up terminating their employment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy PolicyBackgroundsOnline.com&#39;s Privacy PolicyLast updated: June 13, 2017Backgrounds Online is a consumer reporting agency governed by the Fair Credit Reporting Act (&#34;FCRA&#34;) as well as other state and federal laws. It is required by the FCRA, 15 U.S.C. § 1681 et seq. to maintain the confidentiality of allconsumer information. We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. Our privacy policy is intended to describe how we use and handle personal information as it pertains to your usage of our web site located at http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/products-and-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/products-and-services/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#160; Products &amp; ServicesChoose a screening package for the position you&#39;re filling or customize your own. We&#39;ll help you put together a background check that empowers you to identify the right candidate for any job.Screening PackagesCustom Background ChecksBasic Package$29.95A simple, cost-effective screening solution, we consider this option a good introductory background check.Social Security Number TraceCounty Criminal Court Search*National Criminal Database SearchSex Offender Registry SearchTerrorist Watch List SearchBuy Basic PackageStandard Package$49.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/resources/</guid>
      <description>--ResourcesBackgrounds Online provides many free resources for you. Learn about our technology and get useful, relevant information from our blogs, newsletters and other assets.
 State LawsNew state laws are passed every year. We provide details about new and upcoming laws that could impact the hiring process where you operate so you can plan ahead to stay compliant.More InfoBlogCheck our weekly blog for news, tips and updates that are relevant to your business and industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/technology/</guid>
      <description>Our TechnologyWe don&#39;t keep up with the technology curve. We help create it.API &amp; Integration DocumentsConnecting and communicating with our system is simple. We provide services for both submitting screening requests and retrieving results through XML. Results may be easily parsedand formatted to suit your needs. Request our full API documentation to get started and see justhow easy it is to implement our services directly into yoursystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amjadrathod.github.io/why-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amjadrathod.github.io/why-us/</guid>
      <description>Why Backgrounds Online?We’re more than an employment screening company. We are partners who will educate, protect and keep you compliant.Superior Customer ServiceMost of our customers never leave. Those that do, usually return. That’s because we provide truly dedicated service – the kind we like to receive. Our staff focuses on customer service and makes you our top priority.Experience the Backgrounds Online difference for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>